const fs = require('fs');

const quizData = [
  { question: "What is the name of the algorithm used by GPT-4?", options: ["Generative Adversarial Network","Artificial Neural Network","Transformer Architecture","Q-learning"], correct: 2 },
  { question: "What common issue in AI-generated images involves incorrect positioning of body parts, especially noted with fingers?", options: ["Mode collapse","Artifact","Overfit","Latent space"], correct: 1 },
  { question: "What is the name of the company that aims to enhance tunneling speed enough such that establishing a tunnel network is financially feasible, which is owned by Elon Musk?", options: ["Neuralink","SpaceX","Boring Company","OpenAI"], correct: 2 },
  { question: "What is the implantable brain computer capable of translating thoughts into actions?", options: ["Synchron","Emotiv","BrainCo","Neuralink"], correct: 3 },
  { question: "What is the term for the technique used to improve images generated by upscaling in NVIDIA's DLSS technology?", options: ["Raytracing","FSR","sharpening","FPS Boost"], correct: 0 },
  { question: "Name a common test used to determine if a machine can exhibit human-like intelligence.", options: ["AI benchmarking","Turing test","Adversarial test","CAPTCHA"], correct: 1 },
  { question: "Name the thing which revolutionized the ability of computers by enhancing their capabilities and become popular due to the rise of AI, what is that?", options: ["RAM","GPU","TPU","CPU"], correct: 1 },
  { question: "The latest tech innovation that speeds up development by using AI which developed by a company called Cognition?", options: ["Gemini-AI","Copilot","GPT-4","Devin-AI"], correct: 1 },
  { question: "What is the name of the first “computer virus” which targeted APARNET, the precursor to the internet?", options: ["Creeper","Lovebug","Stuxnet","Saaser"], correct: 0 },
  { question: "Until Alan Emtage, a native of Barbados, created the world's first search engine, What is the name of the world’s first search engine?", options: ["Google","Archie","Bing","Yahoo"], correct: 1 },
  { question: "What technology used behind the creation of Satoshi Nakamoto?", options: ["Deep learning","IOT","Block chain","Virtual reality"], correct: 2 },
  { question: "This device, introduced by a Cupertino-based tech giant, marks their entry into a new product category that blends realities. What is the name of this product?", options: ["Meta quest","Vision pro","Holo lens","Playstation VR"], correct: 1 },
  { question: "Python, known for its multi-purpose and dead slow execution, but this parallel computing model enhanced its speed, what is it?", options: ["CUDA","Tensor","Registers","Threads"], correct: 0 },
  { question: "What is the name of the standard communication protocol that is crucial for enabling low-power IoT devices to connect to the internet directly via widely used mobile networks?", options: ["MQTT","SMTP","POP3","API"], correct: 0 },
  { question: "Nokia 6131 first used this technology which enables two devices, such as smartphones and payment terminals, to communicate when they are brought within a few centimeters of each other, name that technology", options: ["Wifi","Zigbee","UPI","NFC"], correct: 3 },
  { question: "Emoji widely used in text-based conversation to reflect one’s reaction, name the person who designed the concept of emoji", options: ["Charles Babbage","Shigeta Kurita","John Macarthy","Fu Jeing"], correct: 2 },
  { question: "What North Carolina-based game company created the 2018 game “Fortnite?”", options: ["Activision","Unity","Epic","Sony"], correct: 2 },
  { question: "What is the official name for the “prove you’re not a robot” tests that websites sometimes require?", options: ["CAPTCHA","ReCAPTCHA","Authentication Test","Verify-Pass"], correct: 0 },
  { question: "Which University offered the first-ever academic program in Computer Science?", options: ["MIT","Prude university","Harvard","Stanford"], correct: 0 },
  { question: "Sonos .Inc, an American-based company, what is it famous for?", options: ["Speakers","Camera","Keyboard","Display"], correct: 0 },
];

const jsonData = JSON.stringify(quizData, null, 2);

fs.writeFileSync('quizData.json', jsonData);

